<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>olives on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/olives/</link>
    <description>Recent content in olives on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/olives/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>cod a la biscayan</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r42/</guid>
      <description>1 pound of cod 1-2 cup olive oil 2 sliced onions 1-2 cup tomato sauce 1-2 cup olives 1 tablespoon capers 2 cloves of garlic 1 pound sliced potatoes 2 roasted ripe peppers 1-4 cup raisins Put the cod in hot water, remove the skin and thorns and cut into medium-sized pieces. In a casserole put litters of cod, onions and potatoes, tomato sauce, olives, capers and raisins, garlic and strips of peppers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>seafood salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</guid>
      <description>1 can of salmon 3 cooked potatoes 2 hard-boiled eggs 6 green and 6 black olives thin slices of onion lettuce leaves 1-2 cup oil 1 teaspoon salt the juice of a lemon 1 tomato in a dish, lettuce leaves, on top of thinly sliced potatoes, onion, salmon season with salt, oil and lemon and garnish with tomato, hard-boiled egg slices and olives. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>serenade</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r16/</guid>
      <description>1 pound of cod 1 sliced onion olives to taste 2 sliced tomatoes French sauce Put the cod in water for a few hours to remove some of the salt Boil, remove the skin and thorns and cut into small pieces. Place the cod in a bowl and garnish with tomato wheels, onions and olives. Pour the French sauce. Serve with other boiled foods: banana, sweet potato, potatoes, etc. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
