<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cornstarch on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/cornstarch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cornstarch on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/cornstarch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>chayote in cream</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r01/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4 chayotes 4 tablespoons cornstarch 3-4 cup sugar 2 egg yolks 1 cup milk 1 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons raisins 2 tablespoons melted butter 1-2 cup cracker meal Directions Split the chayotes lengthwise and boil. When they are soft take out the pulp and mash well. Beat the yolks with the sugar, add salt, and cornstarch, milk, mashed chayotes, butter and potatoes Put on the fire and cook until thickened like a cream Fill the rinds with the cream and sprinkle cinnamon on top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chocolate delight</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r25/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1-2 liter of milk 1 cup grated coconut 6 beaten egg yolks 2 tablespoons cornstarch 5 tablespoons grated chocolate 6 tablespoons powdered sugar Directions Soak the coconut with milk to moisten. In a bowl mix the coconut with yolks, cornstarch and chocolate. Beat and a little by little the sugar and milk, pour in a saucepan and cook over low heat. In order for it not to adhere to the bottom of the saucepan it must be continuously moved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>floating island</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r58/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 heaping tablespoons of cornstarch 3-4 liters of milk (use more milk for thinner cream) vanilla essence 4 very beaten egg whites 4 egg yolks 1-2 cup sugar Directions Beat the egg whites to the point of consistent meringue. Boil the milk with vanilla. Add the preparation of the whites by tablespoons and let them cook for a few minutes. Remove the meringue flakes and drain them on a strainer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
