<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>water on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/water/</link>
    <description>Recent content in water on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/water/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>almond horchata</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r26/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup of almonds 1 1/2 cups of hot water 2 cups of luke warm water 1/2 cup of sugar Directions Steep the almonds in hot water for 5 minutes to remove their shell. Proceed with the previous recipe. Serve very cold and garnish with a cherry. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>baked chicken with duchess puree</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients RECIPE1 1 chicken salt and pepper to taste cognac a quarter pound of butter RECIPE2 2 pounds of potatoes water salt to taste half a pound of butter pepper grated nutmeg 2 egg yolks a quarter of milk cream 6 tablespoons grated cheese Directions RECIPE1 Clean the chicken, wash it and dry it, season it with salt, spray the cogñac and place it in the mold you are going to use for roasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>barley soda</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r36/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 glasses 4 cups of hot water 4 tablespoons barley powder 1 cup sugar 1 1/2 teaspoons juice lemon Directions Mix the barley with a little cold water, add the hot water and boil for a few minutes, stirring constantly. Strain the barley, add the sugar and lemon juice. Serve very cold. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chard salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r27/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 bundles of chards 2 cups of water 1 tablespoon of salt 1/2 cup of oil 1/4 cup of vinegar 1 teaspoon of salt 1/4 teaspoon of pepper Directions Wash and boil the chards, for no more than 5 minutes, in pieces and mix in the oil, vinegar, salt, and pepper. Garnish with rings of onions and tomato. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>corncakes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r45/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups cornmeal 4 cups of water 1 teaspoon salt 1 pound of pork 1 onion 2 ounces of ham 3 tablespoons oil 1 pepper 1 tomato 1 teaspoon salt lard Directions Prepare a thick polenta using cornmeal, water and salt. Grind the other ingredients and add the salt. Simmer. Season to taste. On a greased banana leaf, pour two tablespoons of the polenta and spread it in a circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>creole beef gumbo</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r43/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r43/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup celery with its leaves, cut 2 tablespoons butter 2 1/2 cups chopped tomato 8 cups of water 1 1/4 cup rice 1 1/2 cups onion, chopped fine 1 tablespoon sugar 4 teaspoons salt 1/2 teaspoons Worcestershire sauce Directions Sauté the celery in butter for 3 minutes. Add the tomato and water. Bring to a boil, add the onion, sugar, salt and Worcestershire sauce. Bring to a boil for 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gazpacho</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r39/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 clove of garlic 1/4 teaspoon peppercorns 1/2 teaspoon salt 3 tablespoons of oil 4 cups of water 2 tablespoons vinegar 4 chopped tomatoes 2 chopped onions 2 chopped pickles 2 peppers, chopped Directions Grind the garlic along with the pepper, salt and add the oil, water and vinegar. Strain and add to chopped vegetables. Put in the fridge for several hours and add slices of bread before serving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gypsy-style eggs</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r55/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r55/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients regular amount of oil two garlic 10 or 12 peeled almonds a little piece of bread a few strands of saffron 1/2 teaspoons of cumin a little cinnamon powder boiling water salt 7 eggs Directions In a regular amount of oil we will start by frying two garlic, 10 or 12 peeled almonds, a piece of bread, removing when it is browned. In an almirez you start by crushing a few strands of saffron 1/2 teaspoon of cumin, a little cinnamon powder then the garlic, almonds and bread, soaking with drops of the same oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macaroni with sobrassada</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r20/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound of macaroni 8 cups of water 2 tablespoons salt 1/4 pound of broken ham 1/2 cup oil 2 split onions 1 clove of crushed garlic 1/4 pound of oversized des menuzada 1 can of tomato paste 1 cup water Directions Boil the macaroni in salted water and drain them after cooking. Fry the ham in the oil and add the other ingredients Simmer for 15 minutes. Add the macaroni and stir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oatmeal drink</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r53/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r53/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3/4 cup oatmeal 7 cups of water 1 cup sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla Directions Put the oatmeal in the water for an half an hour and strain. Sweeten and add the vanilla. Serve very cold garnished with lemon wedges. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>orange gelatin cake</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r47/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r47/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 packets of orange-flavored gelatin 2 cups boiling water 1 3/4 cup orange juice fresh fruit Directions Dissolve the gelatin in the boiling water. Add the orange juice. Pour into a 1 liter capacity thread mold and cool until firm. Remove from the pan and pour into a serving plate. In the center of the mold, place fresh fruit. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rice with sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r15/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients sofrito 5 split sausages 1 1/2 pounds of rice 1 teaspoon salt 3 tablespoons butter with annatto 3 cups water Directions Add the sausages, rice and butter with sofrito and cook for two minutes. Add the water and season to taste. Cook until the rice is a little dry, lower the heat, stir two or three times and keep covered until ready to serve. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salvadorean rice and chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups rice coarse salt 5 cups of hot water 1 bay leaf 1 lemon husk lemon juice 6 poultry livers lard 1/2 onion thinly cut 1 glass of marsala wine 1 pinch of salt 1 pinch of black pepper 1 pinch of cinnamon 2 teaspoons rice starch 1 cup warm milk Directions Put in a clay pot the rice with the salt, water, bay leaf, a piece of lemon peel and a little lemon juice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venetian sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients A pound of fine sausage oil water salt three-quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes butter milk one egg for each sausage round Directions A pound of thin sausage is cut into pieces of about 25 centimeters, rolled into rounds, pinned with two toothpicks and fried in oil. Separately, three quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes are cooked in water and salt They are drained once cooked and flattened with a puree machine or with a fork add four tablespoons of butter and half a cup of hot milk, season with a little salt and keep warm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
