<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cheese on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/cheese/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cheese on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/cheese/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>baked chicken with duchess puree</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients RECIPE1 1 chicken salt and pepper to taste cognac a quarter pound of butter RECIPE2 2 pounds of potatoes water salt to taste half a pound of butter pepper grated nutmeg 2 egg yolks a quarter of milk cream 6 tablespoons grated cheese Directions RECIPE1 Clean the chicken, wash it and dry it, season it with salt, spray the cogñac and place it in the mold you are going to use for roasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>baked plantains</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r14/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4 ripe plantains 1/2 pound of cheese broken into long slices butter Directions Peel the plantains. Once peeled cut down center. Bake, after filling with cheese, in a mold with butter. Once golden, prepare a white syrup and serve. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brain pudding</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r41/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 brain 2 beaten eggs 4 tablespoons of breadcrumbs 6 tablespoons grated cheese 2 tablespoons butter 1 teaspoon salt 1/8 teaspoon pepper Directions Boil the brain, mash and strain through a cheesecloth. Add the eggs, bread, cheese, butter, salt and pepper. Season it to taste and pour it into a greased mold. Bake at a temperature of 350 degrees F for 30 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>deviled eggs</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r33/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 12 hard-boiled eggs 1 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper 3 slices of bacon 1/2 cup grated cheese 2 cups bechamel Directions Split each of the hard-boiled eggs in half, to separate the white from the yolks. Mix the yolks. Fry the bacon and break into small pieces. Add to the mixed yolks, season with salt and pepper and fill the egg halves. Mix the white sauce with the cheese, pour over the stuffed eggs and serve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian rice</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 pound chopped onions 4 tablespoons butter 4 ounces of broken ham 3 split tomatoes 3 split anchovies 1 1/2 pounds of rice 3 cups chicken broth 1 minced chicken breast 1/2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Sauté and brown the onions and add the ham, tomatoes, anchovies. Add the rice, stir and sauté. Add the broth and chicken. When the rice is almost dry, add the cheese, stir, and pour into a grease mold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jackfruit pancakes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r12/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups boiled jackfruit 2 tablespoons butter 1/2 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons grated cheese 1 beaten egg Directions Mash the jackfruit, add the salt and butter and mix well. Add the egg, salt and cheese Shape it into small cakes and fry in plenty of hot butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macaroni and Vienna sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r30/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 pound macaroni 1/2 pounds of grated American cheese 2 cups white sauce 2 cans of Vienna sausages Directions Cook the macaroni in plenty of salt water, until soft. Remove from heat, drain them and pour warm water again. Drain again. Make a white sauce with the additional recipe we offered, and add the grated cheese. Cut into wheels several sausages, leaving 6 whole for adornment. Combine the macaroni, sauce, and sausage slices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato fritters</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 1/2 pounds of potatoes 1 tablespoon salt 2 eggs 1 cup grated cheese 1/2 pound butter Directions Boil and mash the potatoes. Add the eggs and cheese and fry in butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tomatoes a la mireille</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r08/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 tomatoes 1 onion 3 eggplants 1 garlic 1 cup white wine 3 egg yolks parsley 1 cup grated cheese cracker meal salt Directions Tomatoes are divided into two and are emptied, seasoned with salt and pepper. Fry with the onion cut into small pieces, the eggplant in thin slices. Sprinkle with white wine. Add the salt to taste, parsley and grated cheese. Let it cool and add the three egg yolks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
