<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sausage on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/sausage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sausage on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/sausage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>macaroni and Vienna sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r30/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 pound macaroni 1/2 pounds of grated American cheese 2 cups white sauce 2 cans of Vienna sausages Directions Cook the macaroni in plenty of salt water, until soft. Remove from heat, drain them and pour warm water again. Drain again. Make a white sauce with the additional ecipe we offered, and add the grated cheese. Cut into wheels several sausages, leaving 6 whole for adornment. Combine the macaroni, sauce, and sausage slices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r48/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 cups cooked potatoes and diced 1 1/2 cup chopped celery 6 tablespoons pepper, chopped 3/4 cup Kraft Mayonnaise 1 tablespoon of onion or garlic salt if you prefer freshly ground pepper lettuce hard-boiled eggs 7 slices of sausage 6 tablespoons tomato dressing Directions Stir the potatoes, celery and pepper with the mayonnaise. Salt and pepper are added to taste. Put a mound of salad on arranged lettuce on a plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rice with sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r15/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients sofrito 5 split sausages 1 1/2 pounds of rice 1 teaspoon salt 3 tablespoons butter with annotto 3 cups water Directions Add the sausages, rice and butter with sofrito and cook for two minutes. Add the water and season to taste. Cook until the rice is a little dry, lower the heat, stir two or three times and keep covered until ready to serve. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venetian sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients A pound of fine sausage aciete water salt three-quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes butter milk one egg for each sausage redondel Directions A pound of thin sausage is cut into pieces of about 25 centimeters, rolled into rounds, pinned with two toothpicks and fried in oil. Separately, three quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes are cooked in water and salt They are drained once cooked and flattened with a puree machine or with a fork add four tablespoons of butter and half a cup of hot milk, season with a little salt and keep warm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
