<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coconut on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/coconut/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coconut on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/coconut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>chocolate delight</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r25/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 liter of milk 1 cup grated coconut 6 beaten egg yolks 2 tablespoons cornstarch 5 tablespoons grated chocolate 6 tablespoons powdered sugar Directions Soak the coconut with milk to moisten. In a bowl mix the coconut with yolks, cornstarch and chocolate. Beat, and a little by little add the sugar and milk. Pour in a saucepan and cook over low heat. In order for it not to adhere to the bottom of the saucepan it must be continuously stirred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>layered pound cake</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r32/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r32/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound cake 1 glass of rum 8 tablespoons grated coconut 10 candied cherries 1 kilogram of dulce de leche Directions The pound cake is cut into layers fine and sprinkled with rum, covering with dulce de leche. It is layered and covered above and around with the same dulce. Sprinkle around dulce and decorate on top with the rest of the dulce. Garnish with candied cherries split in half.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sweet coconut drink</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r31/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups shredded coconut 2 tablespoons melted butter 2 beaten eggs 2 ounces peeled almonds Directions Add the butter and eggs to the shredded coconut. Pour into a flat greased mold. Garnish with almonds. Bake over moderate heat for 20 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
