<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>butter on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/butter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in butter on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/butter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>baked chicken with duchess puree</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients RECIPE1 1 chicken salt at ease pepper cognac a quarter pound of butter RECIPE2 2 pounds of potatoes water salt to taste half a pound of butter pepper grated nutmeg 2 egg yolks a quarter of milk cream 6 tablespoons grated cheese Directions RECIPE1 Clean the chicken, go, wash it and dry it, season it with salt, spray the cogñac and place it in the mold you are going to use for roasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>baked plantains</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r14/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4 ripe plantains 1-2 pounds of cheese broken into long slices butter Directions Peel the plantains. Once peeled cut down center. Bake, after filling with cheese, in a mold with butter. Once golden, prepare a white syrup and serve. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bean omelette</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r11/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound of beans 2 crumbled chorizos 3 beaten eggs 1 teaspoon grated onion 1-4 teaspoon pepper butter Directions Soften the beans and mash them. Add the other ingredients and mix. Put enough butter in the pan to cover the bottom. Pour into the pan, cover and simmer, come back and brown on both sides. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brain pudding</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r41/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 brain 2 beaten eggs 4 tablespoons of breadcrumbs 6 tablespoons grated cheese 2 tablespoons butter 1 teaspoon salt 1-8 teaspoon pepper Directions Boil the brain, mash and strain through a cheesecloth. Add the eggs, bread, cheese, butter, salt and pepper. Season it to taste and pour it into a greased mold. Bake at a temperature of 350 degrees F for 30 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chayote in cream</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r01/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4 chayotes 4 tablespoons cornstarch 3-4 cup sugar 2 egg yolks 1 cup milk 1 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons raisins 2 tablespoons melted butter 1-2 cup cracker meal Directions Split the chayotes lengthwise and boil. When they are soft take out the pulp and mash well. Beat the yolks with the sugar, add salt, and cornstarch, milk, mashed chayotes, butter and potatoes Put on the fire and cook until thickened like a cream Fill the rinds with the cream and sprinkle cinnamon on top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cocada</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r31/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups dulce de coco 2 tablespoons melted butter 2 beaten eggs 2 ounces peeled almonds Directions Add the butter and eggs to the dulce de coco. Pour into a flat greased mold. Garnish with almonds. Bake over moderate heat for 20 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>creole beef gumbo</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r43/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r43/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup celery with its leaves, cut 2 tablespoons butter 2 1/2 cups chopped tomato 8 cups of water 1 1/4 cup rice 1 1/2 cups onion, chopped fine 1 tablespoon sugar 4 teaspoons salt 1/2 teaspoons Worcestershire sauce Directions Sauté the celery in butter for 3 minutes. Put the tomato and water. Bring to a boil, pour the onion, sugar, salt and English sauce. Bring to a boil for 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>grilled lobster</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r54/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r54/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 3-pound lobster butter salt and pepper to taste Directions Cut the lobster lengthwise without removing the shell. Remove the stomach and intestines. Place each half on the grill, resting on the shell. Spread butter and sprinkle with pepper to taste. Simmer for 40 minutes. Serve hot with melted butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian rice</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1-2 pound chopped onions 4 tablespoons butter 4 ounces of broken ham 3 split tomatoes 3 split anchovies 1-1-2 pounds of rice 3 cups chicken broth 1 minced chicken breast 1-2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Brown the onions and add the ham, tomatoes, anchovies, and sauté. Add the rice, stir and sauté. Add the broth and chicken. When the rice is almost dry, add the cheese, stir, pour into a grease mold and sprinkle with ground cracker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jackfruit pancakes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r12/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups boiled jackfruit 2 tablespoons butter 1-2 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons grated cheese 1 beaten egg Directions Mash the jackfruit, add the salt and butter and mix well. Add the egg, salt and cheese Shape it into small cakes and fry in hot, hearty butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>liver fillets</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r51/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r51/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients liver fillets flour salt oil a bay leaf, 50 grams of butter a glass of Marsala wine cooked spinach lard cooked potatoes Directions Cut some liver fillets by touching the telita and nerves and pass them through flour and season with salt. Put in a frying pan half a cup of oil, heat well and brown the encores then add a bay leaf, 50 grams of butter, a glass of Marsala wine, cover and let it boil slowly until the fillets are cooked and the sauce reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>orange cakes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r29/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 300 grams of flour 150 grams of sugar 2 teaspoon baking powder half a teaspoon of salt half a teaspoon of baking soda 100 grams of butter 1 orange Directions Pass through a sifter 300 grams of flour, 150 of sugar, 2 teaspoons filled with baking powder, half salt and a half baking soda. Mix a cup of orange juice with the zest of an orange, 100 grams of barely melted butter, a beaten egg and add it to the other ingredients put in a buttered and floured mold do and cook like the previous ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato cream soup</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r50/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r50/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 tablespoons butter 2 teaspoons salt 1-4 teaspoon pepper 3 tablespoons tri flour go 6 cups of hot milk 1 tablespoon grated onion 2 cups mashed potatoes Directions Prepare the bechamel by melting the butter. Add salt, pepper and flour and stir until it forms a pass. Pour the hot milk and onion and move constantly. When it boils add the mashed potatoes. Serve hot. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato fritters</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 1-2 pounds of potatoes 1 tablespoon salt 2 eggs 1 cup grated cheese 1-2 pound butter Directions Boil and mash the potatoes. Add the eggs and cheese and fry in butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pumpkin purée</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r04/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 cups broth 1-2 pound split pumpkin in pieces 2 tablespoons flour 1 tablespoon mantequi at Directions Boil the pumpkin in the broth. Strain and mash the pumpkin, mix the flour with a little cold broth, add the butter and put on the fire, stirring constantly and add the rest of the broth. Season to taste and serve warm. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rice with sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r15/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients sofrito 5 split sausages 1 1-2 pounds of rice 1 teaspoon salt 3 tablespoons butter with annotto 3 cups water Directions Add the sausages, rice and butter with sofrito and cook for two minutes. Add the water and season to taste. Cook until the rice is a little dry, lower the heat, stir two or three times and keep covered until serving. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>roast chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r05/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 3 lbs. chicken cut into pieces wheat flour, salt and pepper frying fat 1-1-2 cups sifted flour 1 1-2 teaspoon powder baking 1 teaspoon salt 4 eggs 1 1-2 cup milk 3 tablespoons butter or fortified margarine, melted black pepper Directions Put the chicken pieces in a cartridge, with flour, salt and pepper, and shake the cartridge so that the pieces are well covered with flour. In a large skillet, endow the chicken on both sides, in hot fat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salvadorean rice and chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups rice coarse salt 5 cups of hot water 1 bay leaf 1 lemon husk lemon juice 6 poultry livers lard 1-2 onion in fine julienne 1 glass of marsala wine 1 pinch of salt 1 pinch of black pepper 1 pinch of cinnamon 2 teaspoons rice starch 1 cup warm milk Directions Put in a clay pot the rice with the salt, water, bay leaf, a piece of lemon peel and a little lemon juice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuffed chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 4-pound chicken 3 teaspoons salt 3 cloves of crushed garlic half a teaspoon of oregano powder 1 chopped onion 1-1-2 pounds of pork a quarter pound of ham 3 tablespoons butter 2 tablespoons tomato sauce 1 tablespoon raisins Directions Marinate the chicken inside and outside several hours before filling it. Grind the ham and the pork and add the other ingredients seasoning and re llane the chicken. Thing the opening and grease it on the outside with butter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sweet potato pudding</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r46/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r46/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound sweet potato boiled and mashed 1-2 cup sugar 1-4 teaspoon cinnamon 1-4 cup wheat flour 1-4 cup milk 2 tablespoons butter melted 2 beaten eggs 1-4 teaspoon salt Directions Mix the ingredients in the order they appear, beat to join them well. Pour into an engrated mold and cook in a moderate heat oven for 20 to 30 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venetian sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients A pound of fine sausage aciete water salt three-quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes butter milk one egg for each sausage redondel Directions </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
