<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>parsley on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/parsley/</link>
    <description>Recent content in parsley on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/parsley/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>marengo chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r03/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 tender chicken (about 11/2 kilos), broken into 4 pieces 1/2 cup olive oil 3 tablespoons cognac 1 medium onion, chopped 2 tablespoons flour 1 cup dry white wine 1 cube of chicken bouillón 1/4 cup mashed tomatoes 3 sprigs of parsley 1 pinch of dried thyme 1 bay leaf, small 200 grams of fresh mushrooms slices 1 cup toasted croutons Directions Chicken pieces, including giblets, are sprinkled with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>peasant stew</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r37/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r37/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup chickpeas 1 cup peas 3 red chorizos 1 teaspoon oregano 2 bay leaflets 1 sprig of parsley 1 onion 1 pepper oil salt Directions Chickpeas and peas are left to soak from the day before, after washing them well. They are brought to a boil in the same water in which they have dawned. When they take point, the bay leaf, oregano, parsley are added, the onion and peppers are chopped and sautéed in oil with a pinch of salt and this is added along with the chorizos in pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rice croquettes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r38/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups cooked white rice 1/4 teaspoon salt 1 beaten egg 1/2 teaspoon pepper 2 tablespoons chopped parsley 3 tablespoons of milk 1 cup cracker meal or toast Directions Add egg, pepper, salt, parsley, and milk to cooked rice. Form the croquettes and sprinkle with the cracker meal (or toast). Fry them in hot and abundant butter and drain them on absorbent paper. Cheese can be used instead of parsley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tomatoes a la mireille</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r08/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 tomatoes 1 onion 3 eggplants 1 garlic 1 cup white wine 3 egg yolks parsley 1 cup grated cheese cracker meal salt Directions Tomatoes are divided into two and are emptied, seasoned with salt and pepper. They are fried with the onion cut into small pieces, the eggplant in thin slices. They are sprinkled with white wine. Add the salt to taste, parsley and grated cheese. Let it cool and add the three egg yolks Tomatoes are stuffed and sprinkled with cracker meal They are placed in a mold, sprinkled with grated Parmesan cheese and au gratin in the oven for 5 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
