<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>milk on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/milk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in milk on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/milk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>baked chicken with duchess puree</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients RECIPE1 1 chicken salt and pepper to taste cognac a quarter pound of butter RECIPE2 2 pounds of potatoes water salt to taste half a pound of butter pepper grated nutmeg 2 egg yolks a quarter of milk cream 6 tablespoons grated cheese Directions RECIPE1 Clean the chicken, wash it and dry it, season it with salt, spray the cogñac and place it in the mold you are going to use for roasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brain fritters</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r18/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 large brain 200 grams of flour 2 egg yolk milk Directions Prepare a large brain, removing the skin and cooking it in water and salt drain it and cut it into pieces. Put in a bowl the flour, yolks and milk in sufficient quantity to form a soft preparation mix well, add the brains, fry them by tablespoons in hot oil and over moderate heat. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chayote in cream</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r01/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4 chayotes 4 tablespoons cornstarch 3/4 cup sugar 2 egg yolks 1 cup milk 1 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons raisins 2 tablespoons melted butter 1-2 cup cracker meal Directions Split the chayotes lengthwise and boil. When they are soft take out the pulp and mash well. Beat the yolks with the sugar, add salt, and cornstarch, milk, mashed chayotes, butter and potatoes Put on the fire and cook until thickened like a cream Fill the rinds with the cream and sprinkle cinnamon on top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chocolate delight</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r25/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 liter of milk 1 cup grated coconut 6 beaten egg yolks 2 tablespoons cornstarch 5 tablespoons grated chocolate 6 tablespoons powdered sugar Directions Soak the coconut with milk to moisten. In a bowl mix the coconut with yolks, cornstarch and chocolate. Beat, and a little by little add the sugar and milk. Pour in a saucepan and cook over low heat. In order for it not to adhere to the bottom of the saucepan it must be continuously stirred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>creamy potato soup</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r50/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r50/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 tablespoons butter 2 teaspoons salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper 3 tablespoons wheat flour 6 cups of hot milk 1 tablespoon grated onion 2 cups mashed potatoes Directions Prepare the bechamel by melting the butter. Add salt, pepper and flour and stir until it forms a paste. Pour the hot milk and onion and stir constantly. When it boils add the mashed potatoes. Serve hot. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>floating island</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r58/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 heaping tablespoons of cornstarch 3/4 liters of milk (use more milk for thinner cream) vanilla essence 4 very beaten egg whites 4 egg yolks 1/2 cup sugar Directions Beat the egg whites to the point of consistent meringue. Boil the milk with vanilla. Add the preparation of the whites by tablespoons and let them cook for a few minutes. Remove the meringue flakes and drain them on a strainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rice croquettes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r38/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups cooked white rice 1/4 teaspoon salt 1 beaten egg 1/2 teaspoon pepper 2 tablespoons chopped parsley 3 tablespoons of milk 1 cup cracker meal or toast Directions Add egg, pepper, salt, parsley, and milk to cooked rice. Form the croquettes and sprinkle with the cracker meal (or toast). Fry them in hot and abundant butter and drain them on absorbent paper. Cheese can be used instead of parsley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>roast chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r05/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 3 lbs chicken cut into pieces wheat flour, salt and pepper oil 1 1/2 cups sifted flour 1 1/2 teaspoon powder baking 1 teaspoon salt 4 eggs 1 1/2 cup milk 3 tablespoons butter or fortified margarine, melted black pepper Directions Put the chicken pieces in a cartridge, with flour, salt and pepper, and shake the cartridge so that the pieces are well covered with flour. In a large skillet, cover the chicken on both sides, in hot oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salvadorean rice and chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups rice coarse salt 5 cups of hot water 1 bay leaf 1 lemon husk lemon juice 6 poultry livers lard 1/2 onion thinly cut 1 glass of marsala wine 1 pinch of salt 1 pinch of black pepper 1 pinch of cinnamon 2 teaspoons rice starch 1 cup warm milk Directions Put in a clay pot the rice with the salt, water, bay leaf, a piece of lemon peel and a little lemon juice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sweet potato casserole</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r46/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r46/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound sweet potato boiled and mashed 1/2 cup sugar 1/4 teaspoon cinnamon 1/4 cup wheat flour 1/4 cup milk 2 tablespoons butter melted 2 beaten eggs 1/4 teaspoon salt Directions Mix the ingredients in the order they appear, beat to join them well. Pour into a greased mold and cook in a moderate heat oven for 20 to 30 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venetian sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients A pound of fine sausage oil water salt three-quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes butter milk one egg for each sausage round Directions A pound of thin sausage is cut into pieces of about 25 centimeters, rolled into rounds, pinned with two toothpicks and fried in oil. Separately, three quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes are cooked in water and salt They are drained once cooked and flattened with a puree machine or with a fork add four tablespoons of butter and half a cup of hot milk, season with a little salt and keep warm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
