<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>potato on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/potato/</link>
    <description>Recent content in potato on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/potato/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>baked chicken with duchess puree</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients RECIPE1 1 chicken salt and pepper to taste cognac a quarter pound of butter RECIPE2 2 pounds of potatoes water salt to taste half a pound of butter pepper grated nutmeg 2 egg yolks a quarter of milk cream 6 tablespoons grated cheese Directions RECIPE1 Clean the chicken, wash it and dry it, season it with salt, spray the cogñac and place it in the mold you are going to use for roasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>basque-styled cod stew</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r42/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound of cod 1/2 cup olive oil 2 sliced onions 1/2 cup tomato sauce 1/2 cup olives 1 tablespoon capers 2 cloves of garlic 1 pound sliced potatoes 2 roasted ripe peppers 1/4 cup raisins Directions Put the cod in hot water, remove the skin and bones and cut into medium-sized pieces. In a casserole dish, put pieces of cod, onions and potatoes, tomato sauce, olives, capers and raisins, garlic and strips of peppers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>creamy potato soup</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r50/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r50/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 tablespoons butter 2 teaspoons salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper 3 tablespoons wheat flour 6 cups of hot milk 1 tablespoon grated onion 2 cups mashed potatoes Directions Prepare the bechamel by melting the butter. Add salt, pepper and flour and stir until it forms a paste. Pour the hot milk and onion and stir constantly. When it boils add the mashed potatoes. Serve hot. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>liver fillets</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r51/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r51/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients liver fillets flour salt oil a bay leaf, 50 grams of butter a glass of Marsala wine cooked spinach lard cooked potatoes Directions Cut some liver fillets by tucking the tails and nerves and pass them through flour and season with salt. Put in a frying pan half a cup of oil, heat well and brown the encores then add a bay leaf, 50 grams of butter, a glass of Marsala wine, cover and let it boil slowly until the fillets are cooked and the sauce reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato fritters</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 1/2 pounds of potatoes 1 tablespoon salt 2 eggs 1 cup grated cheese 1/2 pound butter Directions Boil and mash the potatoes. Add the eggs and cheese and fry in butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato pie</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r35/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 pounds of potatoes 1 teaspoon salt 2 beaten eggs 4 tablespoons flour 2 cups minced meat filling Directions Boil and mash the potatoes. Add salt, eggs, and flour. Divide into two portions. Put a part in a greased mold so that it covers the entire mold. Pour the ground beef and spread it and rub with the rest of the potatoes. Cook in a moderate oven at 350 degrees F for 30 or 40 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r48/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 cups cooked potatoes and diced 1 1/2 cup chopped celery 6 tablespoons crushed pepper 3/4 cup Kraft Mayonnaise 1 tablespoon of onion or garlic salt if you prefer freshly ground pepper lettuce hard-boiled eggs 7 slices of sausage 6 tablespoons tomato dressing Directions Stir the potatoes, celery and pepper with the mayonnaise. Salt and pepper are added to taste. Put a mound of salad on arranged lettuce on a plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>seafood salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 can of salmon 3 cooked potatoes 2 hard-boiled eggs 6 green and 6 black olives thin slices of onion lettuce leaves 1/2 cup oil 1 teaspoon salt the juice of a lemon 1 tomato Directions In a dish, placed the lettuce leaves Top with thinly sliced potatoes, onion, salmon Season with salt, oil and lemon and garnish with tomato, hard-boiled egg slices and olives. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venetian sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients A pound of fine sausage oil water salt three-quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes butter milk one egg for each sausage round Directions A pound of thin sausage is cut into pieces of about 25 centimeters, rolled into rounds, pinned with two toothpicks and fried in oil. Separately, three quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes are cooked in water and salt They are drained once cooked and flattened with a puree machine or with a fork add four tablespoons of butter and half a cup of hot milk, season with a little salt and keep warm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
