<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ham on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/ham/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ham on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/ham/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>corncakes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r45/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups corn flour 4 cups of water 1 teaspoon salt 1 pound of pork 1 onion 2 ounces of ham 3 tablespoons oil 1 pepper 1 tomato 1 teaspoon salt lard Directions Prepare a hard funche using flour, water and salt. Grind the other ingredients into the machine and add the salt. Simmer. Season at ease. On a greased banana leaf, pour two tablespoons of funche and spread it in a circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian rice</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 pound chopped onions 4 tablespoons butter 4 ounces of broken ham 3 split tomatoes 3 split anchovies 1 1/2 pounds of rice 3 cups chicken broth 1 minced chicken breast 1/2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Brown the onions and add the ham, tomatoes, anchovies, and sauté. Add the rice, stir and sauté. Add the broth and chicken. When the rice is almost dry, add the cheese, stir, pour into a grease mold and sprinkle with ground cracker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macaroni with sobrassada</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r20/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound of macaroni 8 cups of water 2 tablespoons salt 1/4 pound of broken ham 1/2 cup oil 2 split onions 1 clove of crushed garlic 1/4 pound of oversized des menuzada 1 can of tomato paste 1 cup water Directions Boil the macaroni in salted water and drain them after cooking. Fry the ham in the oil and add the other ingredients Simmer for 15 minutes. Add the macaroni and stir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuffed chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 4-pound chicken 3 teaspoons salt 3 cloves of crushed garlic half a teaspoon of oregano powder 1 chopped onion 1 1/2 pounds of pork a quarter pound of ham 3 tablespoons butter 2 tablespoons tomato sauce 1 tablespoon raisins Directions Marinate the chicken inside and outside several hours before filling it. Grind the ham and the pork and add the other ingredients seasoning and re llane the chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuffed sausage</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r59/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r59/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3/4 pounds of ground beef 3/4 pounds of ground pork 2 teaspoons salt 1/2 teaspoon nutmeg 1/4 teaspoon pepper powder 1 egg 2 egg yolks 1/4 cup cognac cracker meal 1/4 pound precooked ham cut into thin slices Directions Place the meats in a bowl and add the salt, nutmeg and pepper. Stir until the ingredients are well mixed. The egg is added and when it is well bound, a yolk is added and after well-bound the second one is added.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
