<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>onion on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/onion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in onion on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/onion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>bean omelette</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r11/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound of beans 2 crumbled chorizos 3 beaten eggs 1 teaspoon grated onion 1-4 teaspoon pepper butter Directions Soften the beans and mash them. Add the other ingredients and mix. Put enough butter in the pan to cover the bottom. Pour into the pan, cover and simmer, come back and brown on both sides. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>breaded meat medallions</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r22/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 pounds of ground beef 1 grated onion 1/2 tablespoon salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper powder 1/4 teaspoon nutmeg 4 eggs 1 1/2 cup cookie powder frying fat 8 toasted bread medallions mustard sauce Directions Place the meat in a bowl and add the onion, salt, pepper and nutmeg. Integrate well add 2 eggs, integrating each one ligating well. Add cracker meal to give consistency to the dough, but it should still be soft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>corncakes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r45/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups corn flour 4 cups of water 1 teaspoon salt 1 pound of pork 1 onion 2 ounces of ham 3 tablespoons lard 1 pepper 1 tomato 1 teaspoon salt lard Directions Prepare a hard funche using flour, water and salt. Grind the other ingredients into the machine and add the salt. Simmer. Season at ease. On a greased banana leaf, pour two tablespoons of funche and spread it in a circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>creamy pumpkin soup</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r52/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r52/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 cups of mashed pumpkin 3 cups bechamel sauce 1 small onion, grated Directions Add onion and bechemel sauce to mashed pumpkin. Bring to a boil and season at ease. Strain and or broth. Serve callente with crackers or toasted bread. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>creole beef gumbo</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r43/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r43/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup celery with its leaves, cut 2 tablespoons butter 2 1/2 cups chopped tomato 8 cups of water 1 1/4 cup rice 1 1/2 cups onion, chopped fine 1 tablespoon sugar 4 teaspoons salt 1/2 teaspoons Worcestershire sauce Directions Sauté the celery in butter for 3 minutes. Put the tomato and water. Bring to a boil, pour the onion, sugar, salt and English sauce. Bring to a boil for 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gazpacho</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r39/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 clove of garlic 1-4 teaspoon peppercorns 1-2 teaspoon salt 3 tablespoons of oil 4 cups of water 2 tablespoons vinegar 4 chopped tomatoes 2 chopped onions 2 chopped pickles 2 peppers, chopped Directions Grind the garlic along with the pepper, salt and add the oil, water and vinegar. Strain and add to chopped vegetables. Put in the fridge for several hours and add slices of bread before serving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian rice</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1-2 pound chopped onions 4 tablespoons butter 4 ounces of broken ham 3 split tomatoes 3 split anchovies 1-1-2 pounds of rice 3 cups chicken broth 1 minced chicken breast 1-2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Brown the onions and add the ham, tomatoes, anchovies, and sauté. Add the rice, stir and sauté. Add the broth and chicken. When the rice is almost dry, add the cheese, stir, pour into a grease mold and sprinkle with ground cracker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>macaroni with sobreasada</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r20/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound of macaroni 8 cups of water 2 tablespoons salt 1-4 pound of broken ham 1-2 cup oil 2 split onions 1 clove of crushed garlic 1-4 pound of oversized des menuzada 1 can of tomato paste 1 cup water Directions Boil the macaroni in salted water and drain them after cooking. Fry the ham in the oil and add the other ingredients Simmer for 15 minutes. Add the macaroni and stir.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>marengo chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r03/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 tender chicken (about 1-1-2 kilos), broken into 4 pieces 1-2 cup olive oil 3 tablespoons cognac 1 medium onion, chopped 2 tablespoons flour 1 cup dry white wine 1 cube of chicken bouillón 1-4 cup mashed tomatoes 3 sprigs of parsley 1 pinch of dried thyme 1 bay leaf, small 200 grams of fresh mushrooms slices 1 cup toasted croutons Directions Chicken pieces, including giblets, are sprinkled with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>peasant stew</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r37/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r37/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup chickpeas 1 cup peas 3 red chorizos 1 teaspoon oregano 2 bay leaflets 1 sprig of parsley 1 onion 1 pepper oil salt Directions Chickpeas and peas are left to soak from the day before, after washing them well. They are brought to a boil in the same water in which they have dawned. When they take point, the bay leaf, oregano, parsley are added, the onion and peppers are chopped and sautéed in oil with a pinch of salt and this is added along with the chorizos in pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato cream soup</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r50/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r50/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 tablespoons butter 2 teaspoons salt 1-4 teaspoon pepper 3 tablespoons tri flour go 6 cups of hot milk 1 tablespoon grated onion 2 cups mashed potatoes Directions Prepare the bechamel by melting the butter. Add salt, pepper and flour and stir until it forms a pass. Pour the hot milk and onion and move constantly. When it boils add the mashed potatoes. Serve hot. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salvadorean rice and chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups rice coarse salt 5 cups of hot water 1 bay leaf 1 lemon husk lemon juice 6 poultry livers lard 1-2 onion in fine julienne 1 glass of marsala wine 1 pinch of salt 1 pinch of black pepper 1 pinch of cinnamon 2 teaspoons rice starch 1 cup warm milk Directions Put in a clay pot the rice with the salt, water, bay leaf, a piece of lemon peel and a little lemon juice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>seafood salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 can of salmon 3 cooked potatoes 2 hard-boiled eggs 6 green and 6 black olives thin slices of onion lettuce leaves 1-2 cup oil 1 teaspoon salt the juice of a lemon 1 tomato Directions in a dish, lettuce leaves, on top of thinly sliced potatoes, onion, salmon season with salt, oil and lemon and garnish with tomato, hard-boiled egg slices and olives. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>serenade</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r16/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound of cod 1 sliced onion olives to taste 2 sliced tomatoes French sauce Directions Put the cod in water for a few hours to remove some of the salt Boil, remove the skin and thorns and cut into small pieces. Place the cod in a bowl and garnish with tomato wheels, onions and olives. Pour the French sauce. Serve with other boiled foods: banana, sweet potato, potatoes, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>simple spaghetti sauce</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r23/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 chopped onion 1/4 cup of oil 4 garlic cloves 1 cup of tomato sauce 1 can of tomatoes 1 bay leaf 1 teaspoon of sugar 1 teaspoon of salt 1/2 teaspoon of ground pepper Directions Fry the onion in the oil. Add the other ingredients and simmer until it thickens, approximately half an hour. Mash and strain. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuffed chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 4-pound chicken 3 teaspoons salt 3 cloves of crushed garlic half a teaspoon of oregano powder 1 chopped onion 1-1-2 pounds of pork a quarter pound of ham 3 tablespoons butter 2 tablespoons tomato sauce 1 tablespoon raisins Directions Marinate the chicken inside and outside several hours before filling it. Grind the ham and the pork and add the other ingredients seasoning and re llane the chicken. Thing the opening and grease it on the outside with butter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tomatoes a la mireille</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r08/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 tomatoes 1 onion 3 eggplants 1 garlic 1 cup white wine 3 egg yolks parsley 1 cup grated cheese cookie powder salt Directions Tomatoes are divided into two and are emptied, seasoned with salt and pepper. They are fried with the onion cut into small pieces the eggplant in thin slices. They are sprinkled with white wine. Add the salt to taste, parsley and grated cheese. Let it cool and add the three egg yolks Tomatoes are stuffed and sprinkled with cookie powder They are placed in a mold, sprinkled with grated Parmesan cheese and au gratin in the oven for 5 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
