<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><row>
        <id>r49</id>
        <paper>DLA</paper>
        <state>FL</state>
        <course>acompañamiento</course>
        <course_en>side</course_en>
        <tags>sin gluten</tags>
        <tags_en>gluten-free</tags_en>
        <ingredients>cebolla; manteca; jamón; tomate; anchoa; arroz; caldo de gallina; gallina; queso</ingredients>
        <ingredients_en>onion; oil; ham; tomato; anchovy; rice; chicken broth; chicken; cheese</ingredients_en>
        <ingredient_list>1/2 libra de cebollas picadas; 4 cucharadas de manteca; 4 onzas de jamón partido; 3 tomates partidos; 3 anchoas partidas; 1 1/2 libras de arroz; 3 tazas de caldo de gallina; 1 pechuga de gallina picada; 1/2 taza de queso parmesano
rallado</ingredient_list>
        <ingredient_list_en>1/2 pound chopped onions; 4 tablespoons butter; 4 ounces of broken ham; 3 split tomatoes; 3 split anchovies; 1 1/2 pounds of rice; 3 cups chicken broth; 1 minced chicken breast; 1/2 cup grated parmesan cheese
</ingredient_list_en>
        <directions>Dore las cebollas y añada el jamón, los tomates, las anchoas, y sofría.; Agregue el arroz, revuelva y sofría.; Agregue el caldo y la gallina.; Cuando el arroz esté casi seco, añada el queso, revuelva, vierta en un molde en grasado y espolvoree con galleta molida.; Ponga en un horno de calor moderado por 15 minutos, o sobre la hornilla con brasas en la tapa.</directions>
        <directions_en>Brown the onions and add the ham, tomatoes, anchovies, and sauté.; Add the rice, stir and sauté.; Add the broth and chicken.; When the rice is almost dry, add the cheese, stir, pour into a grease mold and sprinkle with ground cracker.; Put in a moderate heat oven for 15 minutes, or on the grilled stove on the lid.
</directions_en>
        <title>arroz a la italiana</title>
        <title_en>Italian rice</title_en>
        <url>https://chroniclingamerica.loc.gov/lccn/sn82001257/1957-01-11/ed-1/seq-5/</url>
        <Heading16/>
        <Heading17/>
        <Heading18/>
    </row>