<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>egg on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/egg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in egg on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/egg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>bacon-stuffed eggs</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r33/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r33/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 12 hard-boiled eggs 1 teaspoon salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper 3 slices of bacon 1/2 cup grated cheese 2 cups bechamel Directions Split the eggs in two each. Mash the buds. Fry the bacon and break into small pieces. Add to the mashed yolks, season with salt and pepper and fill the egg halves. Mix the white sauce with the cheese, pour over the stuffed eggs and serve. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>baked chicken with duchess puree</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients RECIPE1 1 chicken salt at ease pepper cognac a quarter pound of butter RECIPE2 2 pounds of potatoes water salt to taste half a pound of butter pepper grated nutmeg 2 egg yolks a quarter of milk cream 6 tablespoons grated cheese Directions RECIPE1 Clean the chicken, wash it and dry it, season it with salt, spray the cogñac and place it in the mold you are going to use for roasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bean omelette</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r11/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound of beans 2 crumbled chorizos 3 beaten eggs 1 teaspoon grated onion 1/4 teaspoon pepper butter Directions Soften the beans and mash them. Add the other ingredients and mix. Put enough butter in the pan to cover the bottom. Pour into the pan, cover and simmer. Make sure to brown on both sides. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brain fritters</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r18/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 large brain 200 grams of flour 2 egg yolk milk Directions Prepare a large brain, removing the skin and cooking it in water and salt drain it and cut it into pieces. Put in a bowl the flour, yolks and milk in sufficient quantity to form a soft preparation mix well, add the brains, fry them by tablespoons in hot oil and over moderate heat. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brain pudding</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r41/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 brain 2 beaten eggs 4 tablespoons of breadcrumbs 6 tablespoons grated cheese 2 tablespoons butter 1 teaspoon salt 1/8 teaspoon pepper Directions Boil the brain, mash and strain through a cheesecloth. Add the eggs, bread, cheese, butter, salt and pepper. Season it to taste and pour it into a greased mold. Bake at a temperature of 350 degrees F for 30 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>breaded meat medallions</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r22/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r22/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 pounds of ground beef 1 grated onion 1/2 tablespoon salt 1/4 teaspoon pepper powder 1/4 teaspoon nutmeg 4 eggs 1 1/2 cup cookie powder frying fat 8 toasted bread medallions mustard sauce Directions Place the meat in a bowl and add the onion, salt, pepper and nutmeg. Integrate well add 2 eggs, mixing each one in well. Add cracker meal to give consistency to the dough, but it should still be soft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chayote in cream</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r01/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r01/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 4 chayotes 4 tablespoons cornstarch 3/4 cup sugar 2 egg yolks 1 cup milk 1 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons raisins 2 tablespoons melted butter 1-2 cup cracker meal Directions Split the chayotes lengthwise and boil. When they are soft take out the pulp and mash well. Beat the yolks with the sugar, add salt, and cornstarch, milk, mashed chayotes, butter and potatoes Put on the fire and cook until thickened like a cream Fill the rinds with the cream and sprinkle cinnamon on top.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chocolate delight</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r25/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 liter of milk 1 cup grated coconut 6 beaten egg yolks 2 tablespoons cornstarch 5 tablespoons grated chocolate 6 tablespoons powdered sugar Directions Soak the coconut with milk to moisten. In a bowl mix the coconut with yolks, cornstarch and chocolate. Beat and a little by little the sugar and milk, pour in a saucepan and cook over low heat. In order for it not to adhere to the bottom of the saucepan it must be continuously stirred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>floating island</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r58/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 heaping tablespoons of cornstarch 3/4 liters of milk (use more milk for thinner cream) vanilla essence 4 very beaten egg whites 4 egg yolks 1/2 cup sugar Directions Beat the egg whites to the point of consistent meringue. Boil the milk with vanilla. Add the preparation of the whites by tablespoons and let them cook for a few minutes. Remove the meringue flakes and drain them on a strainer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gypsy eggs</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r55/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r55/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients regular amount of oil two garlic 10 or 12 peeled almonds a little piece of bread a few strands of saffron 1/2 teaspoons of cumin a little cinnamon powder boiling water salt 7 eggs Directions In a regular amount of oil we will start by frying two garlic, 10 or 12 peeled almonds, a piece of bread, removing when it is browned. In an almirez you start by crushing a few strands of saffron 1/2 teaspoon of cumin, a little cinnamon powder then the garlic, almonds and bread, soaking with drops of the same oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jackfruit pancakes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r12/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups boiled jackfruit 2 tablespoons butter 1/2 teaspoon salt 2 tablespoons grated cheese 1 beaten egg Directions Mash the jackfruit, add the salt and butter and mix well. Add the egg, salt and cheese Shape it into small cakes and fry in plenty of hot butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>orange punch</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r44/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 egg yolks 1 cup sugar 4 cups orange juice 6 egg whites Directions Beat the yolks and sugar together. Add the juice to the yolks mix well and strain. Serve very cold garnished with the meringue. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato fritters</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 1/2 pounds of potatoes 1 tablespoon salt 2 eggs 1 cup grated cheese 1/2 pound butter Directions Boil and mash the potatoes. Add the eggs and cheese and fry in butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato pie</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r35/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r35/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 pounds of potatoes 1 teaspoon salt 2 beaten eggs 4 tablespoons flour 2 cups minced meat filling Directions Boil and mash the potatoes. Add salt, eggs, and flour. Divide into two portions. Put a part in a greased mold so that it shakes the entire mold. Pour the ground beef and spread it and rub with the rest of the potatoes. Cook in a moderate oven at 350 degrees F for 30 or 40 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r48/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 cups cooked potatoes and diced 1 1/2 cup chopped celery 6 tablespoons pepper, chopped 3/4 cup Kraft Mayonnaise 1 tablespoon of onion or garlic salt if you prefer freshly ground pepper lettuce hard-boiled eggs 7 slices of sausage 6 tablespoons tomato dressing Directions Stir the potatoes, celery and pepper with the mayonnaise. Salt and pepper are added to taste. Put a mound of salad on arranged lettuce on a plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rice croquettes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r38/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r38/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups cooked white rice 1/4 teaspoon salt 1 beaten egg 1/2 teaspoon pepper 2 tablespoons chopped parsley 3 tablespoons of milk 1 cup cracker meal or toast Directions Add egg, pepper, salt, parsley, and milk to cooked rice. Form the croquettes and sprinkle with the cracker meal (or toast). Fry them in hot and abundant butter and drain them on absorbent paper. Cheese can be used instead of parsley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>roast chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r05/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 3 lbs. chicken cut into pieces wheat flour, salt and pepper frying fat 1 1/2 cups sifted flour 1 1/2 teaspoon powder baking 1 teaspoon salt 4 eggs 1 1/2 cup milk 3 tablespoons butter or fortified margarine, melted black pepper Directions Put the chicken pieces in a cartridge, with flour, salt and pepper, and shake the cartridge so that the pieces are well covered with flour. In a large skillet, cover the chicken on both sides, in hot oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>seafood salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 can of salmon 3 cooked potatoes 2 hard-boiled eggs 6 green and 6 black olives thin slices of onion lettuce leaves 1/2 cup oil 1 teaspoon salt the juice of a lemon 1 tomato Directions in a dish, lettuce leaves, on top of thinly sliced potatoes, onion, salmon season with salt, oil and lemon and garnish with tomato, hard-boiled egg slices and olives. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuffed sausage</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r59/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r59/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3/4 pounds of ground beef 3/4 pounds of ground pork 2 teaspoons salt 1/2 teaspoon nutmeg 1/4 teaspoon pepper powder 1 egg 2 egg yolks 1/4 cup cognac cracker meal 1/4 pound precooked ham cut into thin slices Directions Place the meats in a bowl and add the salt, nutmeg and pepper. Stir until the ingredients are well mixed. The egg is added and when it is well bound, a yolk is added and after well-bound the second one is added.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sweet coconut drink</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r31/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 cups shredded coconut 2 tablespoons melted butter 2 beaten eggs 2 ounces peeled almonds Directions Add the butter and eggs to the shredded coconut. Pour into a flat greased mold. Garnish with almonds. Bake over moderate heat for 20 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sweet potato pudding</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r46/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r46/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 pound sweet potato boiled and mashed 1/2 cup sugar 1/4 teaspoon cinnamon 1/4 cup wheat flour 1/4 cup milk 2 tablespoons butter melted 2 beaten eggs 1/4 teaspoon salt Directions Mix the ingredients in the order they appear, beat to join them well. Pour into an engrated mold and cook in a moderate heat oven for 20 to 30 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tomatoes a la mireille</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r08/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r08/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 6 tomatoes 1 onion 3 eggplants 1 garlic 1 cup white wine 3 egg yolks parsley 1 cup grated cheese cracker meal salt Directions Tomatoes are divided into two and are emptied, seasoned with salt and pepper. They are fried with the onion cut into small pieces, the eggplant in thin slices. They are sprinkled with white wine. Add the salt to taste, parsley and grated cheese. Let it cool and add the three egg yolks Tomatoes are stuffed and sprinkled with cracker meal They are placed in a mold, sprinkled with grated Parmesan cheese and au gratin in the oven for 5 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venetian sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients A pound of fine sausage aciete water salt three-quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes butter milk one egg for each sausage redondel Directions A pound of thin sausage is cut into pieces of about 25 centimeters, rolled into rounds, pinned with two toothpicks and fried in oil. Separately, three quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes are cooked in water and salt They are drained once cooked and flattened with a puree machine or with a fork add four tablespoons of butter and half a cup of hot milk, season with a little salt and keep warm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
