<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chicken on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/chicken/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chicken on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/ingredientes/chicken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>baked chicken with duchess puree</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r07/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Chicken Recipe 1 chicken salt and pepper to taste cognac a quarter pound of butter Duchess Puree Recipe 2 pounds of potatoes water salt to taste half a pound of butter pepper grated nutmeg 2 egg yolks a quarter of milk cream 6 tablespoons grated cheese Directions Chicken Recipe Clean the chicken, wash it and dry it, season it with salt, spray the cogñac and place it in the mold you are going to use for roasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian rice</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 pound chopped onions 4 tablespoons butter 4 ounces of broken ham 3 split tomatoes 3 split anchovies 1 1/2 pounds of rice 3 cups chicken broth 1 minced chicken breast 1/2 cup grated parmesan cheese Directions Sauté and brown the onions and add the ham, tomatoes, anchovies. Add the rice, stir and sauté. Add the broth and chicken. When the rice is almost dry, add the cheese, stir, and pour into a grease mold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>marengo chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r03/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r03/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 tender chicken (about 11/2 kilos), broken into 4 pieces 1/2 cup olive oil 3 tablespoons cognac 1 medium onion, chopped 2 tablespoons flour 1 cup dry white wine 1 cube of chicken bouillón 1/4 cup mashed tomatoes 3 sprigs of parsley 1 pinch of dried thyme 1 bay leaf, small 200 grams of fresh mushrooms slices 1 cup toasted croutons Directions Chicken pieces, including giblets, are sprinkled with salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>roast chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r05/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r05/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 3 lbs chicken cut into pieces wheat flour, salt and pepper oil 1 1/2 cups sifted flour 1 1/2 teaspoon powder baking 1 teaspoon salt 4 eggs 1 1/2 cup milk 3 tablespoons butter or fortified margarine, melted black pepper Directions Put the chicken pieces in a cartridge, with flour, salt and pepper, and shake the cartridge so that the pieces are well covered with flour. In a large skillet, cover the chicken on both sides, in hot oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuffed chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 4-pound chicken 3 teaspoons salt 3 cloves of crushed garlic half a teaspoon of oregano powder 1 chopped onion 1 1/2 pounds of pork a quarter pound of ham 3 tablespoons butter 2 tablespoons tomato sauce 1 tablespoon raisins Directions Marinate the chicken inside and outside several hours before filling it. Grind the ham and the pork and add the other ingredients seasoning and fill the chicken. Sew the opening and grease it on the outside with butter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
