<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>gluten-free on Recipes</title>
    <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/etiquettas/gluten-free/</link>
    <description>Recent content in gluten-free on Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/etiquettas/gluten-free/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>barley soda</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r36/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r36/</guid>
      <description>6 glasses 4 cups of hot water 4 tablespoons barley powder 1 cup sugar 1 1-2 teaspoons juice lemon Mix the barley with a little cold water, add the hot water and boil for a few minutes, stirring constantly. Strain the barley, add the sugar and lemon juice. Serve very cold. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beef a la parisienne</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r40/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r40/</guid>
      <description>1 1/2 pounds steak meat (beefsteak) 2 cloves of garlic 1 teaspoon salt 3/4 teaspoon pepper black powder 1 teaspoon lemon juice 1 teaspoon cider vinegar 1/2 teaspoon powders chili 1 teaspoon split oregano leaves 2 8-ounce cans of tomato sauce Cut the meat into 4 servings. Mash the garlic and mix with the salt and pepper. Adobe the meat with this everywhere. Combine lemon juice and vinegar, chili powders and oregano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>brain pudding</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r41/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r41/</guid>
      <description>1 brain 2 beaten eggs 4 tablespoons of breadcrumbs 6 tablespoons grated cheese 2 tablespoons butter 1 teaspoon salt 1-8 teaspoon pepper Boil the brain, mash and strain through a cheesecloth. Add the eggs, bread, cheese, butter, salt and pepper. Season it to taste and pour it into a greased mold. Bake at a temperature of 350 degrees F for 30 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cocada</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r31/</guid>
      <description>2 cups dulce de coco 2 tablespoons melted butter 2 beaten eggs 2 ounces peeled almonds Add the butter and eggs to the dulce de coco. Pour into a flat greased mold. Garnish with almonds. Bake over moderate heat for 20 minutes. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cod a la biscayan</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r42/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r42/</guid>
      <description>1 pound of cod 1-2 cup olive oil 2 sliced onions 1-2 cup tomato sauce 1-2 cup olives 1 tablespoon capers 2 cloves of garlic 1 pound sliced potatoes 2 roasted ripe peppers 1-4 cup raisins Put the cod in hot water, remove the skin and thorns and cut into medium-sized pieces. In a casserole put litters of cod, onions and potatoes, tomato sauce, olives, capers and raisins, garlic and strips of peppers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>corncakes</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r45/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r45/</guid>
      <description>2 cups corn flour 4 cups of water 1 teaspoon salt 1 pound of pork 1 onion 2 ounces of ham 3 tablespoons lard 1 pepper 1 tomato 1 teaspoon salt lard Prepare a hard funche using flour, water and salt. Grind the other ingredients into the machine and add the salt. Simmer. Season at ease. On a greased banana leaf, pour two tablespoons of funche and spread it in a circle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>creole beef gumbo</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r43/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r43/</guid>
      <description>1 cup celery with its leaves, cut 2 tablespoons butter 2 1/2 cups chopped tomato 8 cups of water 1 1/4 cup rice 1 1/2 cups onion, chopped fine 1 tablespoon sugar 4 teaspoons salt 1/2 teaspoons Worcestershire sauce Sauté the celery in butter for 3 minutes. Put the tomato and water. Bring to a boil, pour the onion, sugar, salt and English sauce. Bring to a boil for 30 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>floating island</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r58/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r58/</guid>
      <description>3 heaping tablespoons of cornstarch 3-4 liters of milk (use more milk for thinner cream) vanilla essence 4 very beaten egg whites 4 egg yolks 1-2 cup sugar Beat the egg whites to the point of consistent meringue. Boil the milk with vanilla. Add the preparation of the whites by tablespoons and let them cook for a few minutes. Remove the meringue flakes and drain them on a strainer. Strain the milk, beat the yolks with the sugar and add the warm milk and the previously dissolved cornstarch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>frog legs a la Béarnaise</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r13/</guid>
      <description>8 very fresh frog legs Go out at ease Pepper to taste Oil 3 fresh tomatoes 1 cup white wine Lemon juice (in abundance) The legs are seasoned well and sautéed with the oil. Then add the chopped fresh tomato and white wine and lemon juice. Let cool with some fine chopped herbs. Serve in shells. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>gazpacho</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r39/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r39/</guid>
      <description>1 clove of garlic 1-4 teaspoon peppercorns 1-2 teaspoon salt 3 tablespoons of oil 4 cups of water 2 tablespoons vinegar 4 chopped tomatoes 2 chopped onions 2 chopped pickles 2 peppers, chopped Grind the garlic along with the pepper, salt and add the oil, water and vinegar. Strain and add to chopped vegetables. Put in the fridge for several hours and add slices of bread before serving. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italian rice</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r49/</guid>
      <description>1-2 pound chopped onions 4 tablespoons butter 4 ounces of broken ham 3 split tomatoes 3 split anchovies 1-1-2 pounds of rice 3 cups chicken broth 1 minced chicken breast 1-2 cup grated parmesan cheese Brown the onions and add the ham, tomatoes, anchovies, and sauté. Add the rice, stir and sauté. Add the broth and chicken. When the rice is almost dry, add the cheese, stir, pour into a grease mold and sprinkle with ground cracker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>liver fillets</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r51/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r51/</guid>
      <description>liver fillets flour salt oil a bay leaf, 50 grams of butter a glass of Marsala wine cooked spinach lard cooked potatoes Cut some liver fillets by touching the telita and nerves and pass them through flour and season with salt. Put in a frying pan half a cup of oil, heat well and brown the encores then add a bay leaf, 50 grams of butter, a glass of Marsala wine, cover and let it boil slowly until the fillets are cooked and the sauce reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>oatmeal soda</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r53/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r53/</guid>
      <description>3-4 cup oatmeal 7 cups of water 1 cup sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla Put the oatmeal in the water for an inedia hour and strain. Sweeten and add the vanilla. Serve very cold garnished with lemon wedges. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>orange cake</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r47/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r47/</guid>
      <description>2 packets of orange-flavored gelatin 2 cups boiling water 1 3-4 cup orange juice fresh fruit Dissolve the gelatin in the boiling water. Add the orange juice. Pour into a 1 liter capacity thread mold and cool until firm. Remove from the pan and pour into a serving plate. In the center of the mold, place fresh fruit. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>orange punch</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r44/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r44/</guid>
      <description>6 egg yolks 1 cup sugar 4 cups orange juice 6 egg whites Beat the yolks and sugar together. Add the juice to the yolks mix well and strain. Serve very cold garnished with the meringue. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>peasant stew</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r37/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r37/</guid>
      <description>1 cup chickpeas 1 cup peas 3 red chorizos 1 teaspoon oregano 2 bay leaflets 1 sprig of parsley 1 onion 1 pepper oil salt Chickpeas and peas are left to soak from the day before, after washing them well. They are brought to a boil in the same water in which they have dawned. When they take point, the bay leaf, oregano, parsley are added, the onion and peppers are chopped and sautéed in oil with a pinch of salt and this is added along with the chorizos in pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato fritters</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r34/</guid>
      <description>1 1-2 pounds of potatoes 1 tablespoon salt 2 eggs 1 cup grated cheese 1-2 pound butter Boil and mash the potatoes. Add the eggs and cheese and fry in butter. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>potato salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r48/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r48/</guid>
      <description>6 cups cooked potatoes and diced 1 1/2 cup chopped celery 6 tablespoons pepper, chopped 3/4 cup Kraft Mayonnaise 1 tablespoon of onion or garlic salt if you prefer freshly ground pepper lettuce hard-boiled eggs 7 slices of sausage 6 tablespoons tomato dressing Stir the potatoes, celery and pepper with the mayonnaise. Salt and pepper are added to taste. Put a mound of salad on arranged lettuce on a plate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salvadorean rice and chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r19/</guid>
      <description>2 cups rice coarse salt 5 cups of hot water 1 bay leaf 1 lemon husk lemon juice 6 poultry livers lard 1-2 onion in fine julienne 1 glass of marsala wine 1 pinch of salt 1 pinch of black pepper 1 pinch of cinnamon 2 teaspoons rice starch 1 cup warm milk Put in a clay pot the rice with the salt, water, bay leaf, a piece of lemon peel and a little lemon juice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>seafood salad</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r57/</guid>
      <description>1 can of salmon 3 cooked potatoes 2 hard-boiled eggs 6 green and 6 black olives thin slices of onion lettuce leaves 1-2 cup oil 1 teaspoon salt the juice of a lemon 1 tomato in a dish, lettuce leaves, on top of thinly sliced potatoes, onion, salmon season with salt, oil and lemon and garnish with tomato, hard-boiled egg slices and olives. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sparkling coffee soda</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r02/</guid>
      <description>1 1-2 cups of packed cold coffee 1 to 2 tablespoons of sugar 1-2 teaspoon vanilla. Fill the bowl of the electric mixer halfway with well-chopped ice. Then add 1 1 -2 cups of packed cold coffee, 1 to 2 tablespoons of sugar and 1-2 teaspoons of vanilla. Mix for about 2 or 3 minutes. Makes 4 glasses of a rich, frothy coffee drink. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>stuffed chicken</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r21/</guid>
      <description>1 4-pound chicken 3 teaspoons salt 3 cloves of crushed garlic half a teaspoon of oregano powder 1 chopped onion 1-1-2 pounds of pork a quarter pound of ham 3 tablespoons butter 2 tablespoons tomato sauce 1 tablespoon raisins Marinate the chicken inside and outside several hours before filling it. Grind the ham and the pork and add the other ingredients seasoning and re llane the chicken. Thing the opening and grease it on the outside with butter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venetian sausages</title>
      <link>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://recetas.domains.uflib.ufl.edu/en/recetas/r56/</guid>
      <description>A pound of fine sausage aciete water salt three-quarters of a pound of cut and peeled potatoes butter milk one egg for each sausage redondel </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
